♪——照明!
♪- Illumination!
哦。奴才!
Ooh. Minion!
♬是啊，♬噢，当你对着星星许愿时，你的梦想会带你走得很远
♪ Yeah ♪ Ooh ♪ When you wish upon a star ♪ Your dreams will take you very far ♪
♪但是当你对着梦想许愿的时候♪
♪ But when you wish upon a dream ♪
♪生活并不总是像它看起来那样，哦，是的……♪
♪ Life ain't always what it seems, oh, yeah... ♪
别动!AVL !
Freeze! AVL!
♬不管你是谁……嘿!嘿!
♪ No matter who you are... Hey! Hey!
-站住!——抓住她!
- Stop right there! - Grab her!
哦。啊!
Oh. Ah!
——是的,宝贝!-各单位注意。
- Yeah, baby! - Attention, all units.
哇!
Whoa!
当心!
Look out!
-你喜欢吗?——嘿!
- You like that? - Hey!
♪闪亮的星星让你看到♪你的人生真正的样子…♪
♪ Shining star for you to see ♪ What your life can truly be... ♪
重复，所有单位注意，坏人往西走了…♬你的人生真正的样子♬闪耀的星星♬让你看到♬你的人生真正的样子。♪
Repeating, all units, villain is heading westbound... ♪ What your life can truly be ♪ Shining star ♪ For you to see ♪ What your life can truly be. ♪
哦,宝贝!
Ooh, baby!
反恶人联盟是抓不到这个的。
The Anti-Villain League can't catch this.
猜猜谁偷了地图。
Guess who stole the map.
阿利路亚!
Hallelujah!
是啊!我得到这个。
Yeah! I got this.
干得好。
Good work.
传说中的十二宫之石的地图。
The map to the legendary Zodiac Stone.
我们将成为世界上最强大的恶棍。
We will become the most powerful villains in the world.
好了，我们走吧。
Okay, let's get a move on.
我们今晚动身去亚洲。
We leave for Asia tonight.
好的，让我们看看这里。
Okay, let's see here.
算我一个。
I'm in.
你好,漂亮。
Hello, beautiful.
哇!
Whoa!
什么?
What?
哦。
Oh.
哈哈!是的!
Ha ha! Yes!
星座的石头。
The Zodiac Stone.
哇。
Whoa.
很快，这些不可阻挡的野兽的力量就会属于我们。
Soon, the power of these unstoppable beasts will be ours.
啊，我的天啊。
Ah, for crying out loud.
哦。
Oh.
哇。
Whoa.
快点。我的尾巴上有一堆致命的小玩意。
Hurry up. I got a bunch of deadly tchotchkes on my tail.
收到了。
Roger that on the copy.
快点，妹妹。
Step on it, sister.
快点!来吧!
Hurry up! Come on!
走了!
Off! Off!
我得到了它。我拿到石头了。
I got it. I got the stone.
派对结束了，老头。
Party's over, old man.
邪恶六人组有了新老大。
The Vicious Six has a new head honcho.
你刚被耍了!
You just got played for a sucker!
哇!等一等。我创立了这个小组。
Whoa! Hold on. I started this group.
我们是一个团队。
We're a team.
你的忠诚呢?
Where's your loyalty?
哦,请。我们是坏人。
Oh, please. We're villains.
根本就没有这种事。
There's no such thing.
是时候留给下一代了。
It's time for the next generation.
♬Bang，♬Bang，♬Bang，♬Bang, Bang
♪ Bang, bang - ♪ Bang, bang - ♪ Bang, bang ♪ Bang, bang
♪嘿!
♪ Hey!
♪嘿!嘿!
♪ Hey! Hey!
♪嘿!
♪ Hey!
♬砰，♬砰，砰。
♪ Bang, bang ♪ Bang, bang.
安静，同学们。
Quiet down, class.
各位。
People, people.
那么，你长大后想做什么?——哦!噢,噢!
So, what do you want to be - when you grow up? - Ooh! Ooh, ooh!
——萨曼塔。我想成为一名医生。
- Samantha. - I want to be a doctor.
——太棒了。——噢,噢!
- Wonderful. - Oh, oh!
布拉德利。
Bradley.
我想成为一名老师。
I want to be a teacher.
不，你不需要。
No, you do not.
——哦!我,我!——是的。
- Ooh! Me, me! - Yes.
我想成为一名消防员，也是总统，而且还开赛车。是的。
I want to be a fireman who is also the president and-and also drives race cars. Yeah.
令人兴奋的。
Exciting.
你呢，格鲁?
And what about you, Gru?
格勒乌?
Gru?
我吗?
Me?
我想成为……信心满满的。
I want to be... a supervillain.
信心满满的吗?
Supervillain?
——信心满满的。——失败者!
- Supervillain. - Loser!
♬我今天过得很糟糕，很糟糕♬是时候我要按自己的方式走了…♪
♪ I'm having a bad, bad day ♪ It's about time that I get my way... ♪
——凯莉!——爸爸!
- Kelly! - Daddy!
-布雷特!——妈妈!
- Brett! - Mom!
格勒乌!
Gru!
亲吻一个拉妈妈!
Kiss-a la mama!
哦。我最喜欢的小亲戚。
Oh. My favorite tiny relatives.
呃,哦,不。伙计们,来吧。
Eh, oh, no. Guys, come on.
嘿。
Hey.
我要维护自己的形象。
I got an image to uphold here.
好吧。
Okay.
嘿，你们为电影兴奋吗?
Hey, are you guys pumped for the movie?
我们走吧!
Let's go!
哦,不!
Oh, no!
鲨鱼!鲨鱼!
Shark! A shark!
噢!
Oh!
我是弹球奇才。
I am a pinball wizard.
时髦的。时髦的。时髦的。时髦的。时髦的。
Swish. Swish. Swish. Swish. Swish.
时髦的。时髦的。
Swish. Swish.
时髦的。时髦的。时髦的。时髦的。
Swish. Swish. Swish. Swish.
——贝罗。贝罗。——贝罗。
- Bello. -Bello. - Bello.
——贝罗。贝罗。——贝罗。贝罗。
- Bello. Bello. - Bello. -Bello.
你得到的一切。
Everything you got.
多一点。来吧。
A little more. Come on.
-放一些糖屑在上面。
- Put some of those sprinkles on there.
我喜欢那些糖屑。
I like those sprinkles.
Cheese-Ray !Cheese-Ray !
Cheese-Ray! Cheese-Ray!
Cheese-Ray !
Cheese-Ray!
别烦我，兄弟。
Don't cheese me, bro.
揍你!
Pank you!
嗯!如此柔滑，如此美味。
Mmm! So creamy, so delicious.
值得每一个卡路里。
Worth every calorie.
啊,嗯!
Ah, mmm!
♪我今天过得很糟糕♪如果你是针对个人，没关系♪
♪ I'm having a bad, bad day ♪ If you take it personal, that's okay ♪
♬看，这真是太有趣了……♪
♪ Watch, this is so fun to see... ♪
账单，杂志，S&H绿色邮票。
Bills, magazines, S&H Green Stamps.
嗯?
Huh?
噢!
Ooh!
噢,噢,噢!
Ooh, ooh, ooh!
天鳄梨沙拉酱!
Holy guacamole!
我们可以在哪里听?我们可以在哪里听?
Where can we listen? Where can we listen?
你好,格鲁先生。
Hello, Mr. Gru.
我们收到了你的申请加入世界上最好的超级反派团队，邪恶六人组。
We've received your application to the world's best supervillain team, the Vicious Six.
最近有个空缺，而且…- - - ?
A recent opening has become available, - and... - And?
.．.你的面试在明天中午。
...your interview is tomorrow at noon.
Dyn-o-mite !
Dyn-o-mite!
请到主街417号。
Please go to 417 Main Street.
“你不行。”
"You're no good."
“你不行。”嗯哼。
"You're no good." Mm-hmm.
现在，往下划的时候站起来，因为这个邀请会爆炸的，宝贝。
Now, get up on the down stroke, 'cause this invitation is gonna explode, baby.
爆炸吗?哦。
Explode? Oh.
哦，不，不，不，不!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Oot !
Oot!
Oot !Oot !
Oot! Oot!
哦。非常大的新闻，妈妈!
Ooh. Very big news, Mom!
妈妈?
Mom?
什么?
What?
妈，这个大汗淋漓的家伙是谁?
Mom, who is this sweaty guy?
他把房子弄得臭烘烘的。
He's stinking up the house.
我以为你在煮卷心菜。
I thought you were cooking cabbage.
他是我的新导师。
He's my new guru.
告诉你那些奇怪的兄弟们他们最好开始尽职尽责，否则我就把他们踢出去。
Tell your weird buddies they'd better start pulling their weight around here, or I'm kicking them out.
他们破坏了我的圆润氛围。
They are killing my mellow vibes.
嘿!我听说!
Hey! I heard that!
来吧。我们去告诉军队这个好消息吧。
Come on. Let's go tell the troops the good news.
先生们，去地下室，也就是我们新的邪恶巢穴。
Gentlemen, to the basement, aka our new evil lair.
这是太棒了!
This is fantastic!
伙计们，建筑看起来不错。
Oh, construction looks great, guys.
我的第一个邪恶巢穴。
My first evil lair.
鸡皮疙瘩!
Goose bumps!
好吧，为了做一个煎蛋卷，你必须打破一些鸡蛋。
Well, you've got to break a few eggs to make an omelet.
我说的对吗?
Am I right?
-干得好，莱恩——Wh-Wh-What ?
- Oh, great job, Ryan. - Wh-Wh-What?
我说干得好!
I said great job!
关注度高吗?——没关系。
- Wh-What? - Never mind.
阿德里安，麦克，看起来不错。
Adrien, Mack, looking good.
啊。
Ah.
乔，家人好吗?
Joe, how's the family?
嘿。好,好。
Hey. Good, good.
好了，大家都过来。
Okay, everybody, get over here.
现在,听好了。扣你的工作服。
Now, listen up. Buckle your overalls.
抓紧你的护目镜。
Hold on to your goggles.
邪恶六人组想见我。
The Vicious Six wants to meet me.
明天。
Tomorrow.
Mini-Boss !
Mini-Boss!
Mini-Boss !Mini-Boss !
Mini-Boss! Mini-Boss!
好吧，好吧。我不是迷你。
All right, all right. I'm not mini.
请不要那样叫我。
Please stop calling me that.
而且，他们还没有接受我。
And also, they haven't accepted me yet.
你好,奥托。它是什么?
Hello, Otto. What is it?
巴拉,巴拉。
Blah, blah, blah.
啊哈。嗯,th-that……是的,我……嗯哼。
Uh-huh. Well, th-that... Yes, I... Mm-hmm.
我…好吧。
I... Okay.
你知道什么会很有趣吗?
You know what would be fun?
我们来玩安静的游戏吧。
Let's play the quiet game.
哦,哦!安静的游戏!是的,是的!
Oh, oh! The quiet game! Si, si!
不管怎样，谢谢大家今天的辛勤工作。
Anyway, thanks for the hard work today, everyone.
我得去休息了。
I got to go get some rest.
明天是我人生中最重要的一天。
Tomorrow is the biggest day of my life.
小心,世界。
Watch out, world.
格勒乌来了!
Here comes Gru!
——Mini-Boss !Mini-Boss !-我不是…Mini-Boss !Mini-Boss !
- Mini-Boss! Mini-Boss! - I'm not... Mini-Boss! Mini-Boss!
噢!
Oh!
哦，这些家伙是最棒的。
Oh, these guys are the best.
我真不敢相信。
I can't believe it.
呃,Mini-Boss吗?
Uh, Mini-Boss?
我明白，但我需要好好睡一觉，快出去。
Yeah, I get it, but I need a good night's sleep, so get out.
哦。
Oh.
好,好,好。
Okay, fine, fine.
因为你做了噩梦。
Because you had a nightmare.
只是今晚。
But just tonight.
不过我才不信你的鬼话。
I'm not buying the nightmare story, though.
呃,呃,后悔。
Uh, uh, excuse-a.
哦,真的吗?你也吗?
Oh, really? You, too?
——嗯。——进去。
- Mm-hmm. - Get in.
——晚安。——晚安。
- Good night. - Good night.
是的,是的,是的。晚安
Yes, yes, yes. Good night.
——晚安!——哦!
- Good night! - Oh!
我只是想睡一会儿。
Oh, I just want to get some sleep.
♪VNC。
♪ VNC.
邪恶六人组准备改写邪恶的规则。
The Vicious Six is ready to rewrite the rules of villainy.
世界上的恶棍们，三天后，当午夜钟声敲响中国新年开始时，这个坏男孩的力量将被释放出来。
Villains of the world, in three days, when the clock strikes midnight and the Chinese New Year begins, this bad boy's power is gonna be unleashed.
借助十二宫杀手的力量，我们要干掉反恶人联盟。
With the power of the Zodiac, we're gonna take out the Anti-Villain League.
而邪恶六人组将会是这个星球上最强大的反派。
And the Vicious Six will be the most powerful villains on the planet.
你能理解吗?
Can you dig it?
我喜欢吗?我喜欢吗?
Do I dig it? Do I dig it?
我不喜欢。没有什么可挖的。
I don't dig it. There's nothing to dig.
他们以为可以让我自生自灭吗?
They thought they could leave me for dead, huh?
把我像一块老肉一样踢到路边?
Kick me to the curb like a piece of old meat?
哦，他们不知道会发生什么。
Oh, they got no idea what's coming.
——嗯…-我要让他们为他们对我所做的一切付出代价- Knuckles先生?
- Um... - Oh, I'm gonna make them suffer - for what they've done to me. - Uh, Mr. Knuckles?
——哦,男孩。-嘿，Knuckles先生。
- Oh, boy. - Hey, Mr. Knuckles.
什么?
What?
我们只是想确保这周能拿到工资。
We, uh, just wanted to make sure we'd be getting paid this week.
你真会说话。
What a mouth on you.
我用知识付你钱。
I'm paying you with knowledge.
你是谁?噢!
You are? Oh!
总是做好准备。
Always be prepared.
比利时五臂抠鼻器。
The Belgian five-armed nose pick.
立陶宛理发。
The Lithuanian haircut.
那可是世界上最值钱的东西。
That's worth all the money in the world.
嘿，伙计们，算了吧。
Hey, guys, forget about it.
你会得到报酬的。
You're gonna get paid.
但首先，我们得把我的宝石拿回来。
But first, we got to get my stone back.
♬我看到一个邪恶的格鲁正在崛起
♪ I see a bad Gru a-rising
♬我看见一个恶棍在路上!
♪ I see a villain on his way Yee-haw!
♬我要去采访我的英雄们
♪ I'm gonna interview with my heroes ♪
♪他们会喜欢我的，因为我是最好的♪
♪ They're going to love me 'cause I'm the best ♪
♬今晚别搞砸了♬你要加入邪恶六人组了，耶!♪
♪ Don't mess up tonight ♪ You're going to join the Vicious Six, yeah! ♪
♬坏的格鲁乌正在崛起。♪
♪ There is a bad Gru on the rise. ♪
伙计们!
Guys!
哦，你想来吗?
Oh, you want to come.
是的。
Yeah.
对的,正确的。
Right, right.
好吧。
Okay.
当你们找到我并回复了我的招聘广告... ...我就想"这些小土豆是谁啊?
When you guys tracked me down and responded to my "help wanted" ad... ...I was like, "Who are these tiny tater tots?
他们从哪儿弄来这么多牛仔布?”
And where did they get so much denim?"
而你就是不肯放弃。
And you just wouldn't quit.
好吧，我投降。
All right, I surrender.
进来吧。
Come on in.
嗯?
Huh?
从那以后我们有过很多美好的时光，但问题是，邪恶六人组，他们是大联盟，而你们是…太好了,所以……你在老巢的工作…+。
We've had some great times since then, but the thing is, the Vicious Six, they're the big leagues, and you guys are... great, and so... Uh, the job you did on the lair... A-plus.
只是，我在想这个世界上还有很多其他的坏人。
It's just, what I was thinking is that there are a lot of other villains in the world.
你知道吗?
You know?
嗯…
Uh...
不要紧。
Never mind.
听着，我觉得这件事我得单枪匹马。
Look, I think I just need to fly solo on this.
再见，鳄鱼们。
See you later, alligators.
嗯,凯文?凯文!
Uh, Kevin? Kevin!
嗯,Ot-Ot-Otto。O-Otto。
Uh, Ot-Ot-Otto. O-Otto.
走,走,走!
Go, go, go!
嘿，我在走路呢!
Hey, I'm walking here!
哇!
Wow!
噢!我们开始吧。
Ooh! Here we go.
噢!
Oh!
♬我爱你，我需要你♬我想要你，必须拥有你，孩子…♪
♪ That I love ya, I need ya ♪ I want ya, got to have you, child... ♪
对不起。先生?
Excuse me. Sir?
我只是想知道你是否…没有好。
I was just wondering if you're... no good.
你很好。我的错误。
You're good. My mistake.
哦,哦。哦,对不起。
Oh, oh. Oh, sorry.
我不是故意要吓你的。
I didn't mean to scare you.
我只是在尝试我的新发明。
I was just, uh, trying out this new invention of mine.
我叫它“粘手指”。
I call it Sticky Fingers.
或者聪明的粘性。
Or Smart Goo.
我还没想好名字呢。
I-I haven't quite landed on the name yet.
到这里来。
Come here.
我无意中听到你在找东西…特别的。
I overheard you were looking for something... special.
啊,是的。我希望……你没有好。
Ah, yes. I was hoping... you're no good.
我想三号卡座的你们会喜欢听的。
I think you'll enjoy listening in booth three.
这边
Right this way.
啊哈!
Aha!
♬猫抓热…这是它。妈妈的这个词。
♪ Cat scratch fever... This is it. Mum's the word.
保持下来。祝你好运。
Keep it down. Good luck.
让他们尝尝吧，孩子。
Let 'em have it, son.
谢谢,先生……Nefario。
Thanks, Mister... Nefario.
这是Nefario博士。
That's Dr. Nefario.
-给，拿着。——嗯…如果你出名了，记得是谁给了你第一个小玩意。
- Here, take this. - Uh... If you ever get famous, remember who gave you your first gadget.
好吧。
Okay.
如果他对我说我不会怪他
♪ Wouldn't blame him if he said to me ♪
♪你不行，你不行♪
♪ You're no good, you're no good ♪
♬你不行…试着后退。
♪ You're no good... Try backwards.
啊。
Ah.
欢迎来到邪恶六人组。
Welcome to the Vicious Six.
哇。
Whoa.
很……哇!
That is pretty... Whoa!
你好。
Hello.
大家都来面试了吗?
Everybody here for the interview?
我也是。
Me, too.
你们等会有什么安排吗?
So, what do you guys got going on later?
你不怀好意吗?
Are you up to no good?
你要胡闹吗?
You gonna get into some mischief?
好吧。
Okay.
让第一个进来。
Send the first one in.
他们准备好见你了，格鲁先生。
They're ready to see you, Mr. Gru.
哦,很好。
Oh, good.
太好了。
Great.
哦……
Oh...
尊敬的恶棍们，我是格鲁。
Distinguished villains, my name is Gru.
我觉得我说话的声音太大了尽管我们的距离不需要这么大的音量。
I feel like I'm talking too loud even though our proximity doesn't require this kind of volume.
如果你在我十岁的时候告诉我，我有机会成为我最喜欢的恶棍，野指关节，我会说，你脑子里有石头
If you told me when I was ten that I would have the chance to fill the shoes of my favorite villain ever, Wild Knuckles, I would say, "You got rocks in your head."
但现在我11又4 / 4岁了，这就说得通了。
But now that I'm 11 and three quarters, it makes a lot more sense.
好吧，谁让那孩子进来的?
All right, who let the kid in?
我以为他是个小个子。
I thought he was a tiny man.
你怎么了?
What's wrong with you?
你真的认为一个弱小的孩子也能成为坏人吗?
You seriously think a puny little child can be a villain?
嗯,是的。
Um, yes.
我很卑鄙。
I-I am pretty despicable.
你不会想惹我的。
You don't want to cross me.
邪恶是为那些偷取强大古石并大肆破坏的成年人准备的。
Evil is for adults who steal powerful ancient stones and wreak havoc.
而不是那些胖乎乎的小混混他们应该在学校里，学习，休息，吮吸大拇指。
And not for tubby little punks who should be at school, learning, taking a recess, sucking his thumb.
“吸他的……”
"Sucking his..."
等你做了让我印象深刻的事再来。
Come back when you've done something to impress me.
下一个是谁?
Who's next?
我是荣曼，邪恶六人组的下一个成员。
I am Wing Man, the next member of the Vicious Six.
看哪，这是飞行的能力。
Behold, the power of flight!
好了，玩笑结束了。
All right, joke's over.
好戏上演。
Showtime.
这是一个大问题。
This is a big one.
是的,是的。
Yeah, yeah.
到左边。这是正确的。
To the left. That's right.
带他进来，带他进来，伙计们。
Bring him in, bring him in, boys.
每个人都堆!
Everybody pile on!
他拿走了魔法石!
He took the stone!
我要得到他!
I'll get him!
噢!啊!
Oh! Ah!
封锁大楼。
Lock down the building.
噢!噢!
Oh! Oh!
——嗯?——什么?-嗯……这里没什么可看的。
- Huh? - What? -Uh... Nothing to see here.
——哦。-哦，看看你
- Oh. - Oh, look at you.
弗兰普顿是活着!不错的选择。
Frampton Comes Alive! Nice choice.
我…继续走。
I... Just keep walking.
那到底是谁?一个孩子吗?
Who the heck is that? A kid?
哦,伙计们。
Oh, guys.
——贝罗。——Mini-Boss !
- Bello. - Mini-Boss!
你在这里做什么?
What are you doing here?
好了，上车吧。
Okay, just get on.
他往哪边去了?
Which way did he go?
那个小贼来了!
There's that little thief!
去吧!走,走,走!
Go! Go, go, go!
分手了!
Split up!
咚,咚,交付。
Knock, knock. Delivery.
恶魔的孩子!
That demon child!
奥托，把石头带回巢穴。
Otto, take the stone back to the lair.
我要分散他们的注意力。
I'll distract them.
去吧!走,走,走!
Go! Go, go, go!
呃,呃…噢!
Uh, uh... Ooh!
哦,不是现在。
Oh, not now.
加油，加油!
Come on, come on!
噢!
Oh!
是的,宝贝。
Yeah, baby.
我会处理这个问题。
I'll handle this.
希望你能享受你短暂的余生。
Hope you enjoy the rest of your short life.
请工作。
Please work.
快点，快点，快点!
Come on, come on, come on!
耶!
Yay!
我们来找你了，小家伙。
We're coming for you, tiny man.
——是的!——是的!
- Yeah! - Yeah!
乔什，打起精神来。
Josh, pump it up.
起来,起来,起来!
Up, up, up!
♬所有的年轻人♬嘿，伙计♬携带新闻…他们都说那孩子不可能是真正的恶棍。
♪ All the young dudes ♪ Hey, dudes ♪ Carry the news... They all said the kid couldn't be a real villain.
嗯…这孩子刚从世界上最坏的恶棍那里偷了东西。
Well... this kid just stole something from the worst villains in the world.
当我把它拿给他们的时候，他们会说……“我们犯了一个可怕的错误。
When I bring it back to them, they are going to say... "We have made a terrible mistake.
请加入我们的行列。请,格勒乌。”
Please join us. Please, Gru."
我会说:“是的!
And I will say, "Yes!
我将成为恶毒六人组的最新成员。”
I will be the newest member of the Vicious Six."
现在我只需要奥托了。
Now all I need is Otto.
奥托在哪里?
Where is Otto?
嗯，嗯，来吧。
Uh, uh, Otto le come-ay.
不，不是“Otto le come-ay”。
No, not "Otto le come-ay."
他现在需要“来-ay”。
He needs to "come-ay" now.
-奥托!——Mini-Boss !
- Otto! - Mini-Boss!
你就在那里。
There you are.
啊。你明白了吗?
Ah. You got it?
这是……你这是在逗我吗?
Is this... Are you pulling on my legs right now?
奥托，石头在哪里?
Otto, where is the stone?
Le烤饼吗?对了，司康饼。
Le scone? Ah, si, le scone.
哦……
Ooh...
在那里。
Over there.
哦,不!
Oh, no!
哦。
Oh.
亲爱的。亲爱的。
Mi amor. Mi amor.
我…爱……你。
I... love... you.
嗯?
Huh?
你用我的未来换了块宠物石吗!
Did you just trade my future for a Pet Rock?!
嗯…如果吗?
Uh... si?
好吧。
Okay.
奥托，生日派对在哪里举行的?
Otto, where was this birthday party?
呃,呃…
Uh, uh...
这是不可接受的。不能接受的!
This is unacceptable. Unacceptable!
我告诉过你们，你们还没准备好进入大联盟，而你们已经证明了我是对的。
I told you guys that you weren't ready for the big leagues, and you have proven me correct.
你只会把一切都搞砸。
All you do is mess everything up.
起来吗?加油!
Up? Pump it up!
♬跳一小段舞……不许玩，要听音乐!啊!
♪ Do a little dance... No play-a music a! Ah!
我妈妈是对的。
My mom was right.
你不属于这里。
You do not belong here.
你被解雇了!
You're fired!
我要找到那块石头。
I'm going to find that stone.
等我回家，你们最好都走了。
When I get home, you all better be gone.
Mini-Boss……还有，奥托，闭上你的嘴!
Mini-Boss... And, Otto, close your yapper!
哦。
Oh.
乔希。
Josh.
如果,如果。
Si, si.
♪我会和爱情说再见♪没有人在乎我的生死…♪
♪ I'll say goodbye to love ♪ No one ever cared if I should live or die... ♪
嗯,格勒乌。
Uh, Gru.
帮助我。帮助我。
Por favor. Por favor.
♬一次又一次……凯文,没有。
♪ Time and time again... Kevin, no.
我一个人会过得更好。
I will be better off on my own.
♪我只知道没有爱怎么生活♪
♪ And all I know of love is how to live without it ♪
-我好像就是找不到
- ♪ I just can't seem to find it ♪
所以我已经下定决心，我必须独自生活，虽然这不是容易的路
♪ So I've made my mind up ♪ I must live my life alone ♪ And though it's not the easy way ♪
♪我想我一直都知道♪我会对爱说再见♪没有明天♪对于我的这颗心…
♪ I guess I've always known ♪ I'd say goodbye to love - ♪ There are no tomorrows ♪ For this heart of mine...
♪我会发现有人让我相信，让我为之而活…♪
♪ And I'll find that there is ♪ Someone to believe in and to live for... ♪
Mini-Boss !
Mini-Boss!
哦,不。
Oh, no.
对不起。
I'm sorry.
我以为你会对我印象深刻。
I thought you'd be impressed.
我能和贝尔·巴顿通话吗?她会……
Could I just speak to Belle Bottom? She'll...
野生指关节!
Wild Knuckles!
噢!噢!
Oh! Oh!
你还活着吗?
You're alive?
哇。我最喜欢的坏人也是绑架我的人?
Wow. My favorite villain is also my kidnapper?
如果你不杀我，这可能是个好机会。
This could be a great opportunity if you don't kill me.
闭嘴，把石头给我。
Shut up and give me the stone.
哦，是的，那块石头。
Oh, yes, the stone.
事情是这样的。
Here's the thing about that.
这是个有趣的故事。
Kind of a funny story.
给他!
Give it to him!
这一切很快就会变糟。
And it's all going to go south very quickly.
这是什么鬼?
What the heck is this?
孩子，它在哪儿?
Where is it, boy?
我没有!我没有!
I don't have it! I don't have it!
我知道你把它藏起来了。
I know you're hiding it somewhere.
我没有。我没有。我发誓。
I'm not. I'm not. I swear.
我发誓，我宁愿死，把针插进我的眼睛。
Cross my heart and hope to die, stick a needle in my eye.
不过，不要真的这么做。
Don't actually do that, though.
谁给我拿个电话。
Somebody bring me a phone.
打电话回家。
Call home.
这是赎金。
It's ransom time.
不,不,不。我妈妈可能会付钱让你养我!
No, no, no. My mom will probably pay you to keep me!
好一个。
Good one.
电话!
Call!
电话号码。
La telefono.
嗯?
Huh?
贝罗。迷你老板之家。
Bello. La casa de Mini-Boss.
-你是谁?——凯文。
- Who is this? - Kevin.
凯文，小黄人。
Kevin, uh, le Minion.
“凯文勒”什么?
"Kevin le" what?
——勒的奴才。-开什么玩笑?
- Le Minion. - You kidding me?
你有追随者吗?
You got henchmen?
好了，到此为止。
Well, that's the end of that.
M-Mini-Boss吗?
M-Mini-Boss?
听着，你，把石头带到旧金山给我。
Listen, you, bring the stone to me in San Francisco.
格林街6830号。明白了吗?
6830 Green Street. Got it?
给你两天时间，不然你就再也见不到你的小老板了。
Now, you got two days, or you are never going to see your little boss again.
贝罗?贝罗。啊!
Bello? Bello. Aah!
奥托……嗯…
Otto... Uh...
啊!好吧,好吧,好吧。
Ah! Okay, okay, okay.
嗯,嗯。
Mm, hmm.
啊?
Ah?
奥托……O-Okay。如果,如果。
Otto... O-Okay. Si, si.
♪嘿，嚯，我们走吧♪嘿，嚯…奥托……-嗯，嗯，是，是。——好的。走,走,走。
- ♪ Hey, ho, let's go ♪ Hey, ho... Otto... - Uh, uh, si, si. - Okay. Go, go, go.
♬他们正在经历一场强风
♪ They're going through a tight wind ♪
♬孩子们正在失去理智……♪
♪ The kids are losing their minds... ♪
哦?
Oh?
噢!
Oh!
哦,那块石头!
Oh, the stone!
嗯,如果。
Uh, si.
把它给了我叔叔。
Gave that to my uncle.
这更像是他的风格。
It's more his style.
哦。
Oh.
个别…拉石头的!
La-la... la stone-a!
K-Kevin !凯文!
K-Kevin! Kevin!
拉石头的!
La stone-a!
我告诉你。
I told you.
我不知道他去哪了，你个傻逼。
I don't know where he went, you stupid Twinkies.
呃,好吧。
Uh, okay.
呃,pank你。嗯,再见。
Uh, pank you. Eh, bye-bye.
嗯?
Huh?
哦，不酷，伙计。
Oh, not cool, man.
圣Pan-pisco。噢!
San Pan-pisco. Oh!
让我们摇滚起来吧。
Let's rock and roll.
是时候拿回我们的石头了。
Time to get our stone back.
我们来找你了，格鲁先生。
We're coming for you, Mr. Gru.
阿利路亚!
Hallelujah!
呜，呜，呜，呜，呜!
Woop, woop, woop, woop, woop!
粉碎!粉碎!
Smash! Smash!
1109次航班将在27B口起飞。
Flight 1109 will now depart at gate 27B.
啊。贝罗。
Ah. Bello.
呃，三张票，San Pan-pisco。
Uh, trey ticket-as por San Pan-pisco.
旧金山?好吧。
San Francisco? Okay.
你要怎么付款?——啊。
- How will you be paying? - Ah.
嗯…没问题
Uh... No problemo.
哦,太棒了。
Oh, great.
如果你有毛球，我们可以帮你升到头等舱。
You know, if you have any hair balls, we can upgrade you to first class.
出去。
Get out.
-所以我就去了。-我们的两个引擎都失去了推力，我不得不在拉瓜迪亚折返。
- So there I was. - We lost thrust in both engines, and I had to turn back at LaGuardia.
时尚宣言。
Ooh-la-la.
——嗨,莎莉。-嗨。
- Hey, Sally. - Hey.
嗯。
Hmm.
啊。
Ah.
♪我要像鹰一样飞翔-去大海♪像鹰一样飞翔…好吧。我们。
♪ I wanna fly like an eagle - ♪ To the sea ♪ Fly like an eagle... Okay. Vamos.
哦。
Ooh.
贝罗。
Bello.
——花生吗?——哦。是的,请。
- Peanut? - Oh. Yes, please.
啊…呃,花生。
Ah... Mm. Uh, peanut.
——花生。——嗯…花生吗?花生。
- Peanut. - Uh... Peanut? Peanut.
花生吗?
Peanut?
嘿,宝贝,花生吗?
Hey, baby, peanut?
啊?啊?
Ah? Ah?
嗯…哦。
Uh... aw.
嘿!
Hey!
嗯?
Huh?
Hmm?
嗯?
Huh?
嗯。
Hmm.
呃,呃…啊。
Uh, uh... Ah.
哦,贝罗!
Oh, bello!
贝罗。
Bello.
哦,嗯…啊。
Oh, uh... Ah.
你看我，你看不见我。
You see me, you see me not.
哦，哦，哦，哦。
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
没有。没有哈哈。
No. No ha-ha.
你真有勇气，孩子，从邪恶六人组偷东西。
You got real moxie, kid, stealing from the Vicious Six.
我很有勇气，真的吗?
I got moxie, really?
我刚刚得到了Wild Knuckles的赞美吗?
Did I just receive a compliment from Wild Knuckles?
哦，我所有的梦想……现在就要实现了!
Oh, all my dreams... are coming true right now!
这将成为你的噩梦。
Well, it's about to become your nightmare.
欢迎来到我的最新刑具，迪斯科地狱。
Welcome to my newest torture device, the Disco Inferno.
你的手下最好在明天日落前赶到这里，因为就算48小时的迪斯科都杀不死你，刀锋也会。
Your Minions better get here by sundown tomorrow, because if 48 hours of disco don't kill you, the blade will.
不，不，不!
No, no, no, no, no!
石头!石头!
Stone-a! Stone-a!
石头!石头!石头!
Stone-a! Stone-a! Stone-a!
石头!
Stone-a!
石头!石头!
Stone-a! Stone-a!
石头!石头!石头!
Stone-a! Stone-a! Stone-a!
——石头!石头!——嘿!
- Stone-a! Stone-a! - Hey!
石头!石头!
Stone-a! Stone-a!
石头!石头的……
Stone-a! Stone-a...
看地图。
Look-a the map-a.
格勒乌……
Gru...
贝罗!
Bello!
下一站，格林街。
Next stop, Green Street.
再见。
Bye-bye.
嗯?
Huh?
嘿,嘿。看起来。
Hey, hey. Look-a.
Come-ay !Come-ay !
Come-ay! Come-ay!
♬越来越多，越来越多，越来越多……Mini-Boss。
♪ More, more, more... Mini-Boss.
斯图尔特。
Stuart.
——Mini-Boss。-不不不
- Mini-Boss. - No, no, no.
好吧,好吧。
Okay, okay.
呃,呃…
Uh, uh...
好吧。走,走,走。
Okay. Go, go, go.
嗯。
Hmm.
嘿。走,走,走。
Hey. Go, go, go.
嗯?
Huh?
嘿，等一下。
Hey, wait a minute.
贝罗。
Bello.
哦,不!
Oh, no!
闯入者!
Trespassers!
得到他们!
Get 'em!
嘿,你。回来这里!
Hey, you. Come back here!
走,走!
Go, go!
凯文!哦,好的。
Kevin! Oh, okay.
给我滚回来!
Get your little butts back here!
好了，现在，你可能会觉得有点疼。
Okay, now, you might feel a little pinch.
现在有你。
Got you now.
是时候做点什么了。
Time to break some bones.
周末有什么计划吗?
Any plans for the weekend?
深呼吸五次。
Take five deep breaths.
我马上回来。
I'll be right back.
嘿!
Hey!
你喜欢欺负小人物，是吧?
You like picking on little guys, huh?
去睡个午觉吧，老太太。
Go take a nap, old lady.
老夫人?
Old lady?
我是古代少林功夫的大师。
I am a master of the ancient Shaolin art of kung fu.
啊。
Ah.
嗯?
Huh?
哈哈!
Ha-ha!
滚开!
Get lost!
如果你回到我们家，你就死定了。
If you come back to our place, you're dead.
嗯,come-ay。
Uh, come-ay.
哦,pank你。
Oh, pank you.
Pank你…你可以走开来感谢我。
Pank you... You can thank me by going away.
我在工作。
I'm working.
.．.功夫……你想学功夫?
...kung fu... You want to learn kung fu?
贝罗,奇卡。
Bello, chica.
.．.功夫吻，吻?
...kung fu por smoochie, smoochie?
我教书的日子结束了。
My teaching days are over.
这就是我现在的生活。
This is my life now.
.．.功夫帕拉…“迷你老板”。
...kung fu para... para save-a le Mini-Boss.
P-Por有利。
P-Por favor.
语气词。
Ai-ya.
很好。
Fine.
我来教你。
I will teach you.
嘿!
Hey!
那些不是给你的。
Those are not for you.
呃,后悔,后悔。
Uh, excuse-a, excuse-a.
游戏的名字是卖，卖，卖!
The name of the game is sell, sell, sell!
♪啊……
♪ Ah...
什么? !
What?!
格勒乌在哪儿?
Where's Gru?
嗯?我怎么知道?
Huh? How should I know?
这些服装是怎么回事?
What's with the costumes?
万圣节是四个月前的事了。
Halloween was four months ago.
你看起来很愚蠢。走开。
You look stupid. Buzz off.
嘘!
Shoo!
我要把肉变嫩。
I'm getting my meat tenderizer.
让我来帮你吧，亲爱的。
Let me help you with that, dearie.
Uh-uh-uh。别碰我。
Uh-uh-uh. Don't touch me.
现在，那个男孩在哪里?
Now, where's the boy?
我不是故意吓你的。
Oh, I didn't mean to scare you.
别担心。我们不生他的气。
Don't worry. We're not mad at him.
我们只是想…雇佣他。
We just want to... hire him.
他在哪里?
Where is he?
Wild Knuckles, San Pan-pisco。
Wild Knuckles, San Pan-pisco.
野拳套还活着?
Wild Knuckles is alive?
和孩子一起工作。
And working with the kid.
——嗯。——哦。
- Hmm. - Oh.
我们要去旧金山。
We're going to San Francisco.
让我们打它。
Let's hit it.
你最好替我付屋顶的钱。
You had better be paying for my roof.
哦,是的,是的。
Ay, ay, ay.
——哦。-太棒了，是吧?
- Ooh. - Pretty groovy, huh?
我们从一个基本的踢腿开始。
We begin with a basic kick.
现在的你。
Now you.
好吧。
Okay.
没有踢。
No kicking.
这是一个甜瓜锤。这是一个武器。
This is a melon hammer. It's a weapon.
这是弗雷德。他是个笨蛋。
This is Fred. He is a dummy.
永远不要低估一个笨蛋。
Never underestimate a dummy.
——哈。假。——贝罗,弗雷德。
- Ha. Dummy. - Bello, Fred.
现在攻击!
Now attack!
斯图尔特!斯图尔特!
Stuart! Stuart!
弗雷德。
Fred.
怀疑告诉我，我无法折断这根木头。
Doubt tells me I cannot break this wood.
啊哈。
Uh-huh.
但怀疑只存在于头脑中。
But doubt exists only in the mind.
你知道我对自己的大脑说什么吗?
You know what I say to my mind?
现在的你。
Now you.
呃,呃…——嗯?——嗯。
Uh, uh... - Huh? - Mm-hmm.
凯文,凯文,凯文。
Kevin, Kevin, Kevin.
好吧。显然，我们还没有准备好接受哲学。
Okay. Clearly, we are not ready for philosophy.
我们的火车。
Let's just train.
- Ho,嘿!何,嘿!-你愿意带我去-♬Funkytown…——哦!何,嘿!
- Ho, hey! Ho, hey! - ♪ A-won't you take me to - ♪ Funkytown... - Ooh! Ho, hey!
哦，哇，哇，好了，好了。
Oh, whoa, whoa, okay, okay, okay.
-♪小镇-耶!
-♪ Town -Yeah!
你会不会带我去耶!
- ♪ Won't you take me to Yeah!
-♪Funkytown……- Hoo !哈!呼! !哈!
- ♪ Funkytown... - Hoo! Ha! Hoo! Ha!
呼! !
Hoo!
——嗯?——休息。
- Huh? - Rest up.
明天会更糟。
Tomorrow's going to be even worse.
什么,你戒烟?
What, you're quitting?
我说过，等我拿到那块石头，我们就无敌了。
I told you, when I get that stone, we're gonna be unstoppable.
我受够了!
I have had enough!
没有什么比一个年迈的恶棍更可悲的了。
There's nothing sadder than an aging villain.
再见，老家伙!
So long, old man!
伙计们,来吧。
Guys, come on.
我们是一个团队。
We're a team.
♪越来越多，越来越多，越来越多♪你喜欢…♬你喜欢吗?
♪ More, more, more ♪ How do you like... ♪ How do you like it?
♬你喜欢……这是天堂吗?
♪ How do you like... Is this heaven?
我不得不解雇我的手下。
I just had to fire my henchmen.
你知道为什么吗?因为他们没有完成任务。
You know why? 'Cause they weren't getting the job done.
好了，我现在要给你松绑了，因为我…我需要你在家里帮我做点事。
Okay, I'm just gonna untie you now because I-I, uh... I-I need you to do some stuff for me around the house.
这可能是，你知道，呃，有一个…这里有个小公司。
And it might be, you know, uh, kind of nice to have a... a little company around here.
哦。哦,是的。
Oh. Oh, yeah.
两个坏蛋在做家务。
Two villains just doing some chores.
谁知道我们会惹上什么麻烦?
Who knows what kind of trouble we could get into?
那是什么?这就是你邪恶的笑声?
What's that? That's your evil chuckle?
——很明显。-太臭了。
- Obviously. - Well, it stinks.
你听起来像吞了卡祖笛的小丑。
You sound like a clown who swallowed a kazoo.
真的吗?你看起来就像一个经历了生命危机的巫师。
Really? Well, you look like a wizard going through an end-of-life crisis.
别紧张，唐·里克斯。
Easy there, Don Rickles.
唐瑞可是谁?
Who's Don Rickles?
石头的。
Stone-a.
石头!
Stone-a!
石头的……
Stone-a...
伙计。
Dude.
我还以为我们已经失去你了。
Ah, I thought we lost you there for a minute.
嘿，冷静，冷静，冷静，ch…你想试试这个吗，小家伙?
Hey, chill, chill, ch-chill, ch... Hey, you want to try this on, little dude?
拉石头的!
La stone-a!
嘿，嘿，嘿，灵魂兄弟，你要去哪里?
Hey, hey, hey, soul brother, where you jettin' off to?
.．.圣Pan-pisco。
...San Pan-pisco.
哈!弗里斯科迪斯科!
Ha! Frisco disco!
——哇。-今天是你的幸运日，孩子
- Wow. - It's your lucky day, kid.
我正沿着海岸前进。
I'm headed up the coast.
我可以顺路送你。
I could drop you off on the way.
呃!
Yee-haw!
.．.拉石头的!
...la stone-a!
哦,看!
Oh, look-a!
嗯?嘿。
Huh? Hey.
从游泳池开始。
Start with the pool.
这地方得打扫得干干净净。
This place has got to be spick-and-span.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
你看起来就像我妈在感恩节做的烤过头的火鸡。
You look like the overcooked turkey my mom makes on Thanksgiving.
哦,上帝。
Oh, God.
哦,是的。我忘了说，泳池里全是我的宠物鳄鱼。
Oh, yeah. I forgot to mention, the pool is filled with my pet crocodiles.
是啊，好吧，好吧，吓不倒我。
Yeah, well, well, doesn't scare me.
小心。我不能让你失去一只手臂，因为我需要你在这之后换几个灯泡。
Be careful. I can't have you lose an arm, because I need you to change some light bulbs after this.
来，我给你示范一下怎么做。
Here, let me show you how it's done.
贝琪，别闹了。
Betsy, knock it off.
嘿!
Hey!
哇!哦,不。
Whoa! Oh, no.
马文,不,不。阻止这种情况的发生。
Marvin, no, no. Stop that.
哇。的帮助!哦,不。
Whoa. Help! Oh, no.
净!
The net!
我有你!我有你!
I got you! I got you!
我不懂你。
I don't got you.
牵起我的手。
Take my hand.
哇。哇。
Whoa. Whoa.
我有你!
I got you!
你本可以逃跑的，但你…但是你没有。
You could've run, but you... but you didn't.
我告诉过你，你是这世上我最喜欢的反派。
I told you, you are my favorite villain in the world.
我不能让你被鳄鱼吃掉。
I could not let you get eaten by crocodiles.
虽然看那部电影会很酷。
Even though that would've been kind of cool to watch.
所以…你想当大反派，是吗?
So... so you want to be a great villain, huh?
这就是我一直想要的。
That's all I ever wanted.
你想要的,嗯…我不知道，你想让我…要我教你一两招吗?
You want, uh... I don't know, you want me... you want me to teach you a thing or two?
Mm-hmm-hmm !
Mm-hmm-hmm!
很多战士问我，我是怎么成为大师的?
Many fighters have asked me, how did I become a great master?
嘿,看!
Hey, look-a!
即使我们中最小的人也能做伟大的事情。
Even the smallest of us are capable of great things.
你只要深入挖掘，找到你内心的野兽，然后…
You just dig down deep, find your inner beast, and...
嗯…一厢情愿吗?
Uh... gesundheit?
现在你试一试。
Now you try.
嗯…
Uh...
找到你内心的野兽!
Find your inner beast!
停止这种踢。
Stop this kick.
我们还有很多工作要做。
We have a lot more work to do.
是吗?是吗?
Eh? Eh?
凯文，斯图尔特和鲍勃，你们准备好了。
Kevin, Stuart and Bob, you are ready.
不，不，不!
No, no, no, no, no!
准备好颁发你们少年功夫成就徽章了吗。
Ready for your junior kung fu achievement badges.
他们死了。
They're dead.
永远保持在角色里。
always stay in character.
了,爷爷。
Got it, Grandpa.
你介意我们上个厕所吗?
Say, do you mind if we use the john?
波因德克斯特在我们回家前是控制不住的。
Poindexter here can't hold it in till we get home.
啊哈。
Uh-huh.
邪恶银行。
The Bank of Evil.
showtime,孩子。
It's showtime, kid.
听我指挥，别忘了你的指示。
Follow my lead, and don't forget your cue.
你好。我,嗯…我只需要兑现这个。
Hello. I, uh... I just need to cash this.
哦,wowie好!好大的银行啊。
Oh, wowie zowie! What a big bank.
这里有多少保安?
How many security guards are in here?
这个小家伙是谁?
Who's this little guy?
那是我的孙子，他还没学会孩子应该被关注而不是被倾听。
Well, that's my grandson, who still has not learned that children should be seen and not heard.
的孩子。
Kids.
我自己也有个儿子。
I actually have a son of my own.
他看上去很奇怪的。
He looks weird.
别听他的。
Oh, don't listen to him.
你儿子非常，可爱。
Your son is very, uh, cute.
嗯。
Hmm.
哦,不!
Oh, no!
哦。
Oh.
哦,帮帮忙!我看到一道白光。
Oh, help! I'm seeing a white light.
海伦，我来找你了!
Helen, I'm coming for ya!
海伦，我来找你了。
Helen, I'm coming for ya.
哦。的帮助!
Oh. Help!
帮助我的pop-pop !
Help my-my pop-pop!
有人帮助他!
Somebody help him!
嗯?
Huh?
我的爷爷!
My grandpa!
我们需要医生!
We need a doctor!
这是一个大问题。
This is the big one.
——哇!——哦。
- Whoa! - Oh.
你听到了吗?
You hear that?
这是天使甜美的声音。
It's the sweet sound of angels.
的帮助!
Help!
做点什么!
Do something!
我的生活在我眼前闪过。
My life is flashing before my eyes.
不,不,不。另一种方法。
No, no, no. The other way.
另一种方法。
The other way.
好了，大家退后。
All right, everyone stand back.
哦。
Uh-oh.
——明确!-不，等一下等等。
- Clear! - No, wait a minute. Wait.
别放弃我，兄弟。
Don't give up on me now, buddy.
不不不，我感觉好多了。
No, no, no, I'm feeling better.
明确!
Clear!
最大的费用。
Maximum charge.
——明确!——谢谢。
- Clear! - Thank you.
你救了我爷爷。
You saved my grandpa.
嗯,我们……是我们干的吗?
Uh, did we... did we do the heist?
爷爷会说最可怕的事情。
Grandpas say the darndest things.
-你掉了这个。——嗯…
- You dropped these. - Um...
看我买了什么!
Look what I got!
嘿。不坏。
Hey. Not bad.
还不错。
Not bad at all.
我们是一个很好的团队。
We make a good team.
我们该怎么办呢?
We do?
哦,是的。嘿，我们得坚持下去。
Oh, yeah. Hey, we got to keep at it.
等着看我接下来要教你什么吧。
Wait till you see what I'm gonna teach you next.
我不能等待。
I cannot wait.
哦，这会很有趣的。
Oh, this is gonna be fun.
嗯哼。
Mm-hmm.
的要好。Mini-Boss。
Yoo-hoo. Mini-Boss.
好的,斯图尔特……鲍勃……罢工的时间!
Okay, Stuart... Bob... Time to strike!
——Mini-Boss !——要好。
- Mini-Boss! - Yoo-hoo.
啊!他们不是在这里。
Aah! They're not here.
散开去找他们。
Fan out and find them.
旧金山要发生大事了。
Something big's going down in Frisco.
看起来。哦。
Look-a. Ooh.
-找到了。——哇。
- Whoo, there it is. - Whoa.
这是一段艰难的旅程，小家伙。
It's been one heck of a ride, little man.
啊,老兄。
Ah, dude.
你知道，我会想你的。
You know, I'm gonna miss you.
嘿，灵魂兄弟，祝你好运!
Hey, soul brother, good luck!
哇。
Wow.
哦……哦。
Oh... Ooh.
我的朋友，你现在要向老派学习了。
My friend, you're now gonna learn from the old school.
哦,不。
Oh, no.
我不敢相信他们这样对我!
I can't believe they did this to me!
他们知道的都是我教的!
I-I taught them everything they know!
我们是一个团队!
We were a team!
我放弃了。
I give up.
嘿，你是个大坏蛋，而他们是愚蠢的白痴。
Hey, you are a great bad guy, and they are stupid idiots.
我唯一的梦想就是和朋友们做坏事。
Only dream I ever had was doing bad stuff with my buddies.
老了,孤独。
old, alone.
你是老了，但你并不孤单。
Well, you are old, but you're not alone.
好吧。
All right.
听着,老兄。
Listen up, buster.
我们要组建一个新团队，名字叫"可怕的二人组"
We are starting a new team, and it's going to be called The Terrible Twos.
我们以后可以找个更好的名字，但现在我们要找到那块石头让所有人知道你还留着它。
We can find a better name later, but right now we're going to find that stone and show everybody that you still got it.
来吧。你只是个孩子。
Come on. You're just a little kid.
这是结束了。回家了。
It's over. Go home.
-但你说过我们…——回家!
- But you said we... - Go home!
加油！加油我们走吧!
Come on, come on. Let's go!
哇!
Whoa!
奥托?
Otto?
奥托!
Otto!
——呃!-奥托!
- Yee-haw! - Otto!
Hyah !Hyah !
Hyah! Hyah!
嘿!
Hey!
奥托!Mini-Boss !
Otto! It's Mini-Boss!
啊!Mini-Boss !
Ah! Mini-Boss!
——Mini-Boss !-奥托!
- Mini-Boss! - Otto!
看!看!
Look-a! Look-a!
石头的。
Stone-a.
你找到石头了。
You found the stone.
奥托，我真为你骄傲。
Otto, I'm so proud of you.
哦……好了，我们时间不多了。
Oh... All right, we don't have much time.
-我们得把这个交给野拳王。-哦,好的。
- We got to get this to Wild Knuckles. - Oh, okay.
好吧。
Okay.
抓住他!
Get him!
走,走,走!
Go, go, go!
好久不见，小混混。
Long time, no see, punk.
我要带。
I'll take that.
是的!
Yes!
别动!
Don't move!
——嗯?——就在那!别动!
- Huh? - Right there! Freeze!
Anti-Villain联赛。
Anti-Villain League.
你被捕了。
You are under arrest.
喂，喂，喂，各位。
Whoa, whoa, whoa, everybody.
你忘了现在几点了吗?
Did you forget what time it is?
新年快乐!
Happy New Year!
火!
Fire!
坚守阵地。
Stand your ground.
- - - - - -当心!——哇!
- Look out! - Whoa!
哦，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
你要去哪里?嗯?
Where do you think you're going? Hmm?
你偷了我们的东西，现在你要付出代价!
You stole from us, and now you're gonna pay!
享受被撕裂的感觉。
Enjoy being torn apart.
——嘿!-…Mini-Boss !
- Hey! - ...Mini-Boss!
伙计们!
Guys!
哦。我们为什么不公平地决斗呢?
Oh. Why don't we make this a fair fight?
你以为我是认真的。
Oh, you thought I was serious.
快跑!
Run!
不!
No!
你好,叛徒。
Hello, traitors.
还记得我吗?
Remember me?
你。
You.
你可以让我等死，你可以毁掉我的一切，但我不会让你伤害那孩子!
You can leave me for dead, you can destroy everything I own, but I will not let you hurt that kid!
你要去救那孩子吗?
Oh, so you're gonna save the kid?
你和哪支军队?
Yeah, you and what army?
这支军队!
This army!
好吧。这支军队。
Okay. This army.
深挖下来。
Dig down deep.
找到你内心的野兽。
Find your inner beast.
嗯。
Mmm.
奥托!
Otto!
快点!快!
Hurry! Faster!
不!
No!
有你。
Got you.
走,走,走!
Go, go, go!
没有。
No.
离他远点!
Get away from him!
破坏了孩子。
Destroy the kid.
噢!
Oh!
不!
No!
嘿,嘿。被一个小胖子打是什么感觉?
Hey, hey. How does it feel to be beaten by a tubby little punk?
你们太棒了!
You guys were amazing!
功夫……这是从哪里来的?
The kung fu... Where did that come from?
很明显，你们被重新雇用了。
Obviously, you guys are rehired.
——哦。-斯图尔特!
- Oh. - Stuart!
交给你了，先生。
It's all yours, sir.
你想把它放在哪里?
Where do you want it?
你能感觉到吗，先生?在这里。
Can you feel this, sir? Right here.
哦,不。
Oh, no.
野生指关节。
Wild Knuckles.
嘿。
Hey.
你会没事的，对吧?
Y-You're gonna be okay, right?
别担心我，孩子。
Don't worry about me, kid.
我会没事的。
I'll be fine.
最后。
Finally.
你会被关很长很长时间。
You're going away for a long, long time.
是啊，我可不敢打赌。
Yeah, well, I wouldn't bet on it.
没有。
No.
再见，孩子。
See you soon, kiddo.
时尚宣言。
Ooh-la-la.
Wild Knuckles是我最喜欢的反派。
Wild Knuckles was my favorite villain.
我们在一起的时间并不多，但我非常感激我们在一起的时光。
We didn't have much time together, but the time we did have, I'm so grateful for.
我一直在想，你不会看着我长大也不会看着我做那些可怕的事。
I've been thinking about how you won't see me grow up or be there for all the terrible things that I'm going to do.
相信我，肯定会有可怕的事情发生。
And believe me, there are gonna be some awful things.
但我会让你骄傲的。
But I'm going to make you proud.
因为你，我会成为最棒的反派。
I'm going to be the best villain ever because of you.
因为你教会了我什么才是重要的。
Because you taught me what matters.
你一个人做不到任何事。
You can't do anything alone.
找到你的部落，永远不要让他们走。
Find your tribe, and never, ever let them go.
奥托?
Otto?
Si。
Si.
你最好别惹麻烦，孩子。
You better stay out of trouble, kid.
我将过一种美好而诚实的生活。
I will lead a good and honest life.
你还活着吗?
You're alive?
噢!
Oh!
你让我大吃一惊。
You just blew my mind.
你是怎么做到的?
How did you do that?
我等不及要伪造自己的死亡来逃避当局。
I cannot wait to fake my own death to avoid the authorities.
大胆尝试吧，孩子。
Shoot for the moon, kid.
大胆尝试。
Shoot for the moon.
再见，笨蛋!
See you later, suckers!
♬你不能总是得到你想要的
♪ You can't always get what you want ♪
但是如果你试过，你可能会找到，你可能会找到
♪ But if you try sometime ♪ You just might find, you just might find ♪
♪你得到了你想要的♪啊，是啊，是啊…
♪ You get what you need ♪ Ah, yeah ♪ Ah, yeah...
对不起,我们关门了。
Sorry, we're closed.
哇。
Whoa.
我只是想谢谢你。
I just wanted to thank you for this.
效果很好。
Worked like a charm.
好吧，让我开门见山地说吧。
All right, let me cut to the chase here.
我需要一个天才的疯狂科学家。
I need a genius mad scientist.
你想为我工作吗?
You want to come work for me?
不，我受够邪恶了。
No, I am done with villainy.
去快乐的地平线。
Off to happier horizons.
再见,小章。
Goodbye, little chap.
帮助我。
Por favor.
好吧，好吧。
Oh, all right, all right.
好吧。别打脸了。
Fine. Stop with the face.
我在。
I'm in.
想看一些很酷的东西吗?
Want to see something cool?
噢!你在开玩笑吧?
Oh! Are you kidding me?
——“大老板”!——“大老板”!“大老板”!“大老板”!
- Big Boss! - Big Boss! Big Boss! Big Boss!
“大老板”。我很喜欢这样。
"Big Boss." I like that.
♪我们还能走得更远♪我们不停地跑，不要回头♪
♪ We can make it further ♪ We running and don't look back ♪
♪这是隧道尽头的一道光
♪ It's a light at the end of the tunnel ♪
♪如果你坚持下去♪但是我知道任何一分钟♪当你的手指像啪的一声掰起来♪
♪ If you stay on track ♪ But I know any minute ♪ When your fingers turn it up like snap ♪
♪失去这样太难了♪嘿，让我们做吧♪世界各地♪我们要打开阳光♪
♪ So hard to lose like that ♪ Hey, let's do it ♪ All around the world ♪ We gotta turn up the sunshine ♪
♬我们要打开阳光♬
♪ We gotta turn up the sunshine ♪
♬想想吧♬所有的男孩和女孩♬你要打开阳光♬
♪ Think about it ♪ All the boys and girls ♪ You gotta turn up the sunshine ♪
♬你要把阳光打开♬
♪ You gotta turn up the sunshine ♪
♬说这是个漫长的夜晚，漫长的夜晚
♪ Said it's been a long night, long night ♪
♪等着亮，等着亮
♪ Waiting for the light, waiting for the light ♪
♪让我们走吧♪走遍世界♪我们要打开阳光♪
♪ Let's do it ♪ All around the world ♪ We gotta turn up the sunshine ♪
♬我们要把它调大♬让它很难失去像那样的♬
♪ We gotta turn it up ♪ Make it hard to lose like that ♪
♪如果这样的天气让你皱眉
♪ If this weather makes you frown ♪
♪有些人会让你倒下♪
♪ And some people get you down ♪
♪记住♪爱，就像声音♪声音越大越好♪如果里面没有歌♪
♪ Remember ♪ Love, like sound ♪ It's better when it's loud ♪ And if there's no song inside ♪
♪我们可以一起把光带来
♪ We can bring the light together ♪
♪日日夜夜♪我们在内心闪耀♪开大，开大♪开大，开大♪
♪ Day or night ♪ We're shining from inside ♪ Turn up the, turn it up ♪ Turn up the, turn it up ♪
♪开大一点，开大一点♪打开阳光♪开大一点，开大一点♪开大一点，开大一点♪
♪ Turn up the, turn it up ♪ Turn up the sunshine ♪ Turn up the, turn it up ♪ Turn up the, turn it up ♪
♪打开，打开♪打开阳光♪世界各地♪我们要打开阳光♪
♪ Turn up the, turn it up ♪ Turn up the sunshine ♪ All around the world ♪ We gotta turn up the sunshine ♪
♬我们要打开阳光♬
♪ We gotta turn up the sunshine ♪
♬想想吧♬所有的男孩和女孩♬你要打开阳光♬
♪ Think about it ♪ All the boys and girls ♪ You gotta turn up the sunshine ♪
♬你要把阳光打开♬
♪ You gotta turn up the sunshine ♪
♬说这是一个到处都是的世界我们要把阳光打开
♪ Said it's been a ♪ All around the world ♪ We gotta turn up the sunshine ♪
♬我们得把它调大♬让它很难失去像那样。♪
♪ We gotta turn it up ♪ Make it hard to lose like that. ♪
♬我要搬到一个适合我的地方
♪ Gotta make a move to a town that's right for me ♪
♬时间让我不停地走
♪ Time to keep me movin'
♬让我充满活力地前行♬
♪ Keep me groovin' with some energy ♪
♬嗯，我说说看，说说看
♪ Well, I talk about it, talk about it ♪
♬说说看，说说看
♪ Talk about it, talk about it ♪
♬谈论它，谈论它，谈论移动♬
♪ Talk about it, talk about it, talk about movin' ♪
♪要走了♪要走了♪要走了♪要走了
♪ Gotta move on ♪ Gotta move on ♪ Gotta move on
♪你会不会带我去♬♬Funkytown♪你会不会带我去♬♬Funkytown♪你会不会带我去♬♬Funkytown
♪ Won't you take me to ♪ Funkytown ♪ Won't you take me to ♪ Funkytown ♪ Won't you take me to ♪ Funkytown ♪ Won't you take me to ♪ Funkytown
♪你会不会带我去♬♬Funkytown♪你会不会带我去♬♬Funkytown♪你会不会带我去♬♬Funkytown。
♪ Won't you take me to ♪ Funkytown ♪ Won't you take me to ♪ Funkytown ♪ Won't you take me to ♪ Funkytown ♪ Won't you take me to ♪ Funkytown.
♬♬感觉好点了♬现在我们通过了♬感觉好点了，因为我忘记你了♬
♪ Feeling better ♪ Now that we're through ♪ Feeling better 'cause I'm over you ♪
♬我得到了教训，它给我留下了伤疤
♪ I learned my lesson, and it left a scar ♪
现在我知道你到底是什么样子了
♪ Now I see how you really are ♪
♪你不行，你不行♪
♪ You're no good, you're no good ♪
♪你一点都不好♪宝贝，你一点都不好♪我再说一遍♪你一点都不好，你一点都不好♪
♪ You're no good ♪ Baby, you're no good ♪ I'm gonna say it again ♪ You're no good, you're no good ♪
♬你一点都不好♬宝贝，你一点都不好
♪ You're no good ♪ Baby, you're no good
♪我伤了一颗温柔又真实的心
♪ I broke a heart that's gentle and true ♪
♬我为你这样的人心碎了
♪ Well, I broke a heart over someone like you ♪
♬我将跪着请求他的原谅
♪ I'll beg his forgiveness on bended knee ♪
如果他对我说♬我不会怪他
♪ I wouldn't blame him if he said to me ♪
♪你不行，你不行♪
♪ You're no good, you're no good ♪
♪你一点都不好♪宝贝，你一点都不好♪我再说一遍♪你一点都不好，你一点都不好♪
♪ You're no good ♪ Baby, you're no good ♪ I'm gonna say it again ♪ You're no good, you're no good ♪
♬你一点都不好♬宝贝，你一点都不好
♪ You're no good ♪ Baby, you're no good
♪我在拒绝你，宝贝，我要走我的路了
♪ I'm turning you down, baby, and I'm going my way ♪
♪忘了你吧，宝贝，因为我要离开♪
♪ Forget about you, baby, 'cause I'm leaving to stay ♪
♪你不行，你不行♪
♪ You're no good, you're no good ♪
♬你不行，宝贝，你不行我再说一遍你不行，你不行
♪ You're no good ♪ Baby, you're no good ♪ I'm gonna say it again ♪ You're no good, you're no good ♪
♬你不好♬宝贝，你不好♬哦，哦，不♬你不好，你不好♬
♪ You're no good ♪ Baby, you're no good ♪ Oh, oh, no ♪ You're no good, you're no good ♪
♬你一点都不好♬宝贝，你一点都不好。
♪ You're no good ♪ Baby, you're no good.